(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHOOSHES)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
(DAISY SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(GYM MEMBERS PANTING)
(PANTING CONTINUES)
(ROPE WHOOSHING)
(CLANKING)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES)
- (MUSIC FADES OUT)
- (WATER SPUTTERING)
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
- DAISY: (MUFFLED) Lou-Lou!
- (WATER SQUELCHING)
- (BATHROOM DOOR OPENS)
- DAISY: Lou-Lou!
- (LOU SIGHS)
(WATER SQUELCHING)
- There you are.
- Hey, Daisy.
Looks like you've got
your hands full.
LOU: Yep!
(TOILET FLUSHING)
(WATER CHOKING)
(GURGLING)
- (SARCASTICALLY) Hurray.
- Nice.
(GLOVES SNAPPING)
- (DAISY HUMMING)
- (FAUCET SQUEAKS)
(WATER RUNNING)
What's up, Daisy?
Was wondering if, um,
maybe you wanted
to meet up later?
Go to Winkie's.
Oh!
I gotta help Beth
with some stuff...
I got to help her.
It's boring. (CHUCKLES)
Aw! Poor Lou-Lou.
Always looking out for her, sis.
You know, you gotta remember
your own needs too.
I have some stuff to finish
up here too though, so...
(CHUCKLES) You've got time.
Hey, you should have
one on me tonight.
Oh, you don't...
You don't have to do that.
Why not? It's fine.
Have fun. Rain check.
But...
- (LOU SNAPPING FINGERS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGN CRACKLES, CLICKS)
(DOOR CREAKS, SLAMS)
- (PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
- (LIGHTER FLICKERS)
LOU: Hey, buddy.
(CAT MEOWS)
ALLEN CARR: (OVER RADIO)
When you smoke a cigarette,
you inhale a drug
called nicotine.
You could replace
the word drug with poison.
Like anything that is not
built on solid foundations,
the brainwashing is as fragile
- as a house of cards...
- (MICROWAVE DINGS)
ALLEN CARR:
and will collapse
in an instant.
All you have to do is
give it a shake.
(LOU BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (COUCH SQUEAKING)
- (CAT PURRING)
JJ: (GRUNTS) Yeah,
you like that dick?
- (SEAT SQUEAKING)
- Oh!
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, fuck!
(GRUNTING)
(JACKIE SIGHS)
Oh, that was...
that was magical.
(JACKIE SIGHS)
JJ: Ah, fuck, yeah.
(WINDOW SQUEALING)
So... So should
I call you, or?
What?
- About the job?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
(COINS CLINKING)
Swing by tomorrow.
Hey, careful where you sleep
around here.
It's dangerous.
JACKIE: Okay. (CHUCKLES)
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(MUSIC PLAYING
THROUGH CAR RADIO)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
(CARS WHOOSHING)
(PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES)
Ah!
(JACKIE PANTING)
ALLEN CARR: (OVER RADIO)
I'd describe the withdrawal
from nicotine as a mild, empty,
slightly insecure feeling.
I've also stated that
the only reason
a smoker lights up
is to relieve that feeling.
- All smokers are caught up...
-  (BRAKES SCREECH)
ALLEN CARR:
in the same trap.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
(SIGHS) Okay.
We're running a little late.
Nothing to worry about.
BILLY: You'll never catch me!
KID: Running too fast!
- (BILLY SCREAMS)
- Whoa! You okay, bud?
(CHUCKLES) Slow down.
- I lost a tooth, Lou.
- What?
Shucks, man.
You gotta be more careful.
Hey, Billy.
Quit hanging off her.
BETH: Come on, you guys.
Let's get all
our stuff together.
Aunt Lou's gonna
drive you to school.
KID 1: Mom! He's calling me...
BETH: Can you open this?
Boys, come get your things.
- KID 1: Mom!
- Come on, ready?
Okay.
- How's my makeup?
- KID 2: Mom, he is cheating.
- Ready, set, go!
- KID 1: I'm not.
You cheated last time.
JJ: Hey, Bethy Boopski?
- You girls goin' to the store?
- Why? You want something?
Can you grab me some smokes.
I'm just...
I don't wanna be late.
I don't think I'll have time.
BETH: Yeah, I could...
I can come...
- JJ: Yeah?
- BETH: drop it off.
- JJ: There you go.
- Aren't we late? No!
Late for school?
Something like that?
KID 1: Dad! Dad!
- Bye.
- Bye, baby.
- Later, my dudes.
- KID 2: Bye, Dad.
- KID 1: Bye!
- (KEYS JANGLING)
KID 2: Mom!
KID 1: Mom!
- (BETH SIGHS)
- (DOOR CLOSES)
KID 1: I don't know
where my bag is.
- Where is it?
- (BILLY SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOTS ECHOING)
JJ: Since Die Hard came out,
fucking everyone wants
to try the Beretta.
We're, uh, we're setting up
a new indoor range out there.
How's it going, guys?
Uh, we got the beginners'
range out there...
We also got long distance,
moving target, novelty...
Get... Get a lot of tourists
come out for the day.
Fuckin' crazy-ass
foreigners mostly.
Uh, that's the canteen.
Sandwiches, drinks.
Get a little wild if you want.
All right, we're gonna
head this way.
JACKIE: Should I be nervous
or something? (CHUCKLES)
JJ: No, just...
Just don't make me look
- like an asshole.
- JACKIE: (CHUCKLES) Okay.
JJ: You know,
just stand up straight.
- (CHUCKLES)
- JACKIE: I'll do my best.
Oh, watch out for that.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
LOU SR: Yeah.
Boss, now a good time?
LOU SR: Good as any.
(GUNSHOTS ECHOING IN DISTANCE)
(CHUCKLES) Wow.
Cool. What is that?
LOU SR:
One of my Hercules larvae.
Just giving his bed
a little spruce.
They like things moist and cozy.
Fuck, yeah. They do.
(SOFTLY) Yeah.
Oh, uh. This here is Jackie.
- Uh, this is Mr. Langston.
- Hi.
JJ: She needs a job.
Says she'll do anything.
I figured we could use
some spare hands.
Yeah, you like guns?
- (SPRAY BOTTLE SPRITZING)
- Not really.
What the fuck are
you doing here then?
Anyone can feel strong
hiding behind a piece of metal.
I prefer to know
my own strength.
Is that right?
(TRANSFORMATION PLAYING
OVER GYM SPEAKERS)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
WOMAN: Excuse me,
the end toilet is blocked.
It's overflowing.
Excuse me?
- The end toilet is blocked.
- Then use the other one.
(WOMAN SIGHS)
(GYM MACHINE CLANKING)
♪ Rust to dust, us to them ♪
♪ Change your mind
Change your skin ♪
♪ Life to death
Weak to strength ♪
O'RILEY: Can I get
a Mountain Dew?
♪ Cash a check
Change your sex ♪
- O'RILEY: Hey!
- (GYM MACHINE CLANKING)
- The machine's over there.
- O'RILEY: It's broken.
(COINS CLANKING)
There you go.
You're Lou Langston's daughter.
- So?
- He's an old friend of mine.
How is your old man?
My old man?
He's a piece of shit.
We don't talk.
Pretty sure
his friends know that.
And your mom, do you know
where I could find her?
- Why?
- O'RILEY: Just to talk.
Well, I'll tell you what.
When you're feeling
more friendly, give us a call.
(JACKIE LAUGHING)
CHESTER: You're nice.
Can we talk?
- I'm Jackie.
- Jackie.
- LOU: Closing.
- (SWITCHES CLANKING)
CHESTER: Whoa!
We're still in here.
LOU: We're closed, fuck off.
CHESTER: Jackie.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(EXHALES)
- Hey.
JACKIE: Can I steal one?
Yeah.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
(JACKIE CHUCKLES)
Is this your place?
No, I just work here.
Okay.
You were looking
pretty good in there.
Yeah?
You got some
pretty serious lines going.
- (DOOR OPENS)
- CHESTER: Jackie!
- There you are.
- (LOU CLEARS THROAT)
CHESTER: Ladies.
If that's all right
with you, Lou?
Hey, we're gonna go
grab a drink right now
- if you wanna come with us?
- Thanks. I'm good here.
CHESTER: (CHUCKLES) Babe.
You know, Lou here is
a grade A dyke, right?
Is that so?
(CHUCKLES) Funny, come on.
- (CHESTER GROANS)
- JACKIE: Touch me...
- (GRUNTS)
- Whoa! Ay!
MIKE: Whoa, man. She's a girl.
LOU: Hey, hey, hey!
MIKE: I'm sorry about that.
CHESTER: You crazy bitch.
- Yeah, here we... Come on, now.
- I was being nice.
- Fuck you!
- LOU: Fuck him! Let's go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING
ON RADIO)
LOU: (CHUCKLES)
You cooling off out here?
You wanna ice yourself?
You gotta be careful
around here, I'm telling you.
That could've gotten
a lot worse.
I could take him.
Oh... Sorry.
So where did you appear from?
- Oklahoma.
- Really?
Yeah, I've been
hitchhiking for a while now.
(CHUCKLES) Are you heading
anywhere particular?
So there's finals
for this bodybuilding contest
next month in Vegas.
Um... Gonna give it
a shot. (CHUCKLES)
I'm just laying low here
while I train.
Cool.
Um, most times
when people hear that,
I get this look like...
(CHUCKLES) Yeah,
I think I know that look.
Is that why you left home?
Oklahomans not
into muscle chicks?
Yeah, not so much. (CHUCKLES)
The place I'm from,
everyone's a farmer,
goes to church twice a week,
that kind of thing.
So how does
an Oklahoma farm girl
get into bodybuilding.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, my folks adopted me
when I was 13.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
And I was a fat kid.
So, kind of got bullied a lot.
- Shit.
- JACKIE: No, it's good.
Taught me to fight back.
LOU: Mmm.
So you're gonna win
this competition.
- And then what?
- I don't know.
I didn't think
that far ahead yet.
Yeah, I think I know that one.
(CHUCKLES)
You want me
to show you something?
- Okay.
- You have to stay here.
I'll be back.
(JACKIE SIGHS)
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING
OVER RADIO)
So maybe this is dumb.
I don't know, I mean...
You're probably
all set with these.
But, ta-da!
Are these yours?
Yeah. How am I doing?
Hmm?
Thanks, but I...
I can't afford them.
(CHUCKLES)
I mean, they're free.
The guys here order 'em in bulk
from, like, Germany or Romania.
They're fucking everywhere.
I'll just give them to you.
Do you not do this shit?
JACKIE: Uh...
Au naturelle, baby.
All right.
Your body, your choice.
You wanna do a little bit?
I think 150 is, kind of,
the smallest dose you can do
and if you have four weeks,
you'll barely notice it,
but it'll build up gradually
and just give you that
little... edge.
Where do you want it?
In the butt.
- Then turn around.
- (CHUCKLES)
Fuck.
(LOU CLEARS THROAT)
- Okay.
- Okay, incoming.
JACKIE: Mmm. (CHUCKLES)
- Done.
- (JACKIE SIGHS)
- How does it feel?
- (JACKIE EXHALES)
(CHUCKLES)
LOU: Feel it already?
You're, like, boom, boom!
It's all over it immediately.
Like Popeye eating spinach.
JACKIE: (CHUCKLES) So stupid.
(JACKIE MOANING)
(LOU MOANS)
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You're not, like, some fucking
straight girl, right?
- Just trying shit out?
- (JACKIE CHUCKLES)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
- (THUDDING)
- JACKIE: Ow!
LOU: Oh, shit, sorry.
Holy, shit!
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
LOU: Holy, fuck.
(JACKIE EXHALES)
(CRACKS)
(WHISK CLATTERING)
(OIL SIZZLING)
JACKIE: Hey!
Hey.
- (SIGHS)
- (COFFEE POURING)
So I gotta...
I gotta go to work today,
but do you, maybe,
wanna hang out later?
LOU: (BLOWS SMOKE)
You got a job already?
Yeah, I'm, uh...
I'm waitressing
at this shooting range place
just outside of town.
It's like, ton of gun nuts
and weirdos.
Pay's pretty good though.
(LOU SCOFFS)
Oh, man don't work there.
- Why not?
- My dad runs it.
JACKIE: (GASPS) Oh my, God.
I met him yesterday.
- LOU: Fun.
- Wait. The bug guy?
- LOU: Yeah, the bug guy.
- (PLATES CLATTERING)
So where are you staying?
Um, I'm actually not sure yet.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
What does that mean?
(MOUTHFUL) I was gonna ask
if maybe I could...
crash here couple of nights.
I mean, like, until
I get paid, you know, like...
Until I can afford
a room somewhere.
(MUMBLES)
You can stay here.
I can just sleep on the couch.
No, shut the fuck up.
You can stay here.
(JACKIE CHUCKLES)
- This is delicious.
- Good.
I mean, like, you know,
next time, maybe,
- take the yolks out, but...
- Oh, yeah.
JACKIE: Mmm-hmm.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
(NICE MOVER PLAYING)
(GUN COCKING)
(SHOTS FIRING)
CHORUS: ♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
JACKIE: And then we do
our first pose,
which is a double front bicep.
(GRUNTS) Super strong,
and confident, relaxed, right?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
WOMAN:
♪ I'm your transformer ♪
♪ Call me Marlene ♪
♪ Call me Gino ♪
♪ That's me you know ♪
♪ I'm your transformer ♪
♪ Call me Marlene ♪
♪ Call me Gino ♪
♪ That's me you know ♪
(WEIGHTS CLANKING)
♪ I like it ♪
♪ Je I'aime ♪
♪ Mi piace ♪
♪ Nice mover ♪
♪ Ring up Studio 54 New York ♪
- ♪ Nice mover ♪
- CHORUS: ♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
WOMAN: ♪ That's me you know ♪
(INDISTINCT YELLING
THROUGH TV SPEAKERS)
♪ I'm your transformer ♪
♪ Call me Marlene ♪
♪ Call me Gino ♪
♪ That's me you know ♪
♪ I like it ♪
♪ Je I'aime ♪
♪ Mi piace ♪
♪ Nice mover ♪
♪ Ring up Studio 54 New York ♪
- ♪ Nice mover ♪
- CHORUS: ♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
♪ That's me you know ♪
JACKIE: Why don't you want me
working for your dad?
LOU: (SIGHS)
We just don't get along.
JACKIE: How come?
'Cause you like girls?
No, he didn't care about that.
That's cool of him.
LOU: He's not cool.
He's a fucking psycho.
(JACKIE GRUNTS)
WOMAN: ♪ I like it ♪
♪ Je I'aime ♪
♪ Mi piace ♪
♪ Nice mover ♪
♪ Ring up Studio... ♪
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
- ♪ Nice mover ♪
- CHORUS: ♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
- ♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
- WOMAN: ♪ Nice mover ♪
♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
- ♪ Baby don't laugh ♪
(GUNSHOT FIRES)
JACKIE: What about
your mom? (PANTING)
What?
She's gone...
She's... It's, um...
- (JACKIE PANTING)
- It's been, like, 12 years.
JACKIE: You mean she's dead?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
No, she's gone.
(PANTS, GRUNTS)
What's wrong?
Why are you stopping?
(JACKIE GROANS)
LOU: Come on, let's go.
- Come on.
- (LIGHTER CLICKS)
- Up, up, up, up.
- (JACKIE GRUNTS)
(GASPS, YELLS)
God, fuck!
- Oh, Lou, ew.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (NAIL CRUNCHING)
- Ah! Hmm.
I can get a job
somewhere else if you want.
- Do what you want.
- (GUN FIRES)
(WIND BLOWING)
(GUN FIRES)
That's not what
I'm paying you for.
I'm on my break, sir.
Come on.
Come on!
If you work here, you should
at least know the basics.
Line her up.
(JACKIE INHALES, EXHALES)
LOU SR: You only have
to be very, very gentle.
(JACKIE EXHALES)
(TARGET SQUEAKS)
A bit more powerful
than a punch, huh?
One more time, line it up.
- Okay.
- That's it. Nice and easy.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
JACKIE: Will you come
with me to Vegas?
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
I want you to see me win.
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, of course.
But, you know,
if you don't win, that's okay.
Right?
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
(GIGGLES)
Jesus.
(GRUNTS)
Afterwards, let's
just keep driving.
Where?
California.
Yeah, if I win.
I can get a job as a trainer,
find a place by the beach,
swim in the ocean.
All that stuff.
Yeah, I've never been
anywhere but here.
Why not?
(WATER GURGLING)
(PEACEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(SLURPS, GULPS)
(MUG THUDS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
So, is the, um...
When is the contest?
- This Thursday.
- BETH: Mmm.
How are you feeling?
JACKIE: Mmm. Good, I think.
LOU: (CHUCKLES)
She's gonna knock 'em out.
BETH: Yeah, you look amazing.
(GASPS) Ooh, food.
Thanks.
- More?
- JJ: Yeah.
- BETH: Pineapple?
- No.
BETH: You guys
will love Vegas. It's wild.
JACKIE: I've heard.
Have you gone?
BETH: We went
for our honeymoon, actually.
JJ: Stupid... (GRUNTS)
Fucking things.
- BETH: You need help, hon?
- No, it's fine.
- You need a fork?
- No.
BETH: Just hold...
JJ: I got it.
- (HESITATES)
- I'm so sorry. I am so sorry.
- That's gonna stain.
- I know, I know.
What... What are you...
You can't just
rub my dick in the middle
of the restaurant.
I'm sorry.
(CHOPSTICKS CLATTERING)
Please don't.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(TOILET FLUSHING)
- (BANGS ON DOOR)
- (DOOR SQUEAKING)
What the fuck?
If you touch her
one more time...
JJ: What? What is it, Lou?
It'll be the last
fucking thing you do.
What the fuck did she tell you
this time, huh?
She doesn't have
to tell me shit. I have eyes.
Why don't you look closer
at your new girlfriend,
then, huh?
Instead of interfering in shit
you don't know about.
Yeah. Yeah, I met her
first night
she rocked up into town.
Took her out back of Daggers.
Gave it to her right there
in the parking lot.
She wanted that job
so fucking bad.
Let me tell you.
Although, I guess...
not as bad as she wanted
a free fucking
gym membership, huh?
(DOOR OPENS)
(LOU EXHALES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
JACKIE: Are you gonna be like
this the rest of the night?
Want me to drop you
off somewhere?
Drop me off?
- JJ's?
- (JACKIE SIGHS)
Fuck, I knew that's why
you're being so weird.
- (BRAKES SCREECH)
- Babe.
You fucked him.
I didn't know
who he was or anything.
I hadn't even met you yet.
I met you the day
after you got here.
So what? Fuck.
So you'd fuck guys?
- (JACKIE SIGHS)
- I specifically asked you...
I like both.
I guess it doesn't
really matter who it is,
as long as they
hook you up with a job,
or a place to stay,
take out your egg yolks.
Did I get it?
Fuck you.
Yeah?
Hey, where
the fuck are you going?
- Where does it look like?
- LOU: Nowhere.
How could you fuck
that guy, baby?
Did you enjoy it?
'Cause he's
beyond sickening like...
Like, a fucking scumbag.
He beats the crap
out of Beth, Jack.
She's completely brainwashed.
She's the only reason
I stick around.
But maybe you think that
I don't have an actual life
outside of helping you
with your dumb shit.
Fuck you!
Of course, I do. But you don't
tell me anything.
I'm telling you now.
Look, look...
That's what's going on.
That's what's always
been going on.
The cops don't do anything
because she won't press charges.
I don't know
what the fuck to do.
I'm sorry, I didn't...
I didn't...
share that with you.
(SIGHS)
You don't think
I have horror stories, Lou.
Huh? I got plenty.
(SIGHS) You don't...
You don't understand.
This guy, I wanna...
I wanna do really...
I wanna do really bad...
I... I wanna fuckin' kill him.
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
Get back in the car.
- Close the door, come on.
- (ENGINE REVVING)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
(LIGHTER CLANKS)
(FAUCET SQUEAKS)
(WATER RUNNING)
(JACKIE EXHALES)
(LOU SNIFFLES)
Just give me a second.
(GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING)
(LOU BREATHING HEAVILY)
I thought you quit.
- (GRUNTS)
- LOU: This doesn't count.
I'm wanna stretch you.
I wanna see how far you can go.
(LICKS FINGERS)
(JACKIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
Do you put your fingers
inside when you fuck yourself?
(JACKIE CHUCKLES)
How do you do it?
You wanna show me?
Come on, show me.
Is that really how you do it?
(JACKIE CHUCKLES)
(GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SOFTLY) Good girl.
(JACKIE MOANING)
Oh, shit.
(GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES)
I love you.
I love you, too.
- (PHONE RINGING)
- (LOU GROANS)
(CHUCKLES)
- JACKIE: Mmm.
- Yeah?
Yeah. (CLEARS THROAT)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, is... Okay, this is 08?
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
LOU: Oh!
(EXHALES)
Hey. (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Oh, my God.
- (GRUNTS)
- (KEYS CLANKING)
NURSE: Paramedics picked
her up at 3:00 a.m.
Still waiting for her
to come round.
I'm not sure.
Sometime late last night.
LOU: Where the fuck is he?
OFFICER: If you're referring
to the husband
he's at the station
giving a statement.
LOU: A statement?
We're clear. We know.
He did this.
OFFICER: Ma'am, no one knows
exactly what happened.
LOU: Have you seen her?
OFFICER: We're gonna wait
until your sister wakes up
and then we're gonna ask
if she wants to press charges.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
(LOU EXHALES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(LOU SR SIGHS)
(LOU BREATHING SHAKILY)
I'll make sure she gets
everything she needs.
(LOU SNIFFLES)
It's best we take care
of JJ ourselves.
He'll regret this.
That's what you said last time.
LOU SR: She wouldn't
wanna wake up
and find her husband in jail.
LOU: I wasn't
thinking about jail.
(SCOFFS) She wouldn't
want him dead either.
I'd like to respect her wishes.
That's big of you.
Don't worry, little Bethany.
(HUMMING)
- (LOU BREATHING SHAKILY)
- LOU SR: It's all gonna heal.
(LOU CRYING)
I'm sorry, Lou.
- (METAL CLANKING)
- LOU: (GRUNTS) Fuck!
(GRUNTING)
Ah! God, ah!
- (GRUNTING)
- (NAILS SCRATCHING)
(LOU CRYING)
(CRYING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(BREATHES SHARPLY)
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPS)
LOU SR: (OVER SPEAKER)
JJ, we gotta talk.
Pick up the phone.
- (GLASS CLINKING)
- (ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPING)
- (ICE CLINKING)
- (WHISKEY POURING)
(JJ SIGHS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Hello?
(DISTANT MUFFLED VOICES)
(DOG BARKING)
- (BIRD SQUAWKING)
- (WINGS FLAPPING)
- Shut the fuck up!
- (JACKIE GRUNTS)
(JJ YELLS)
- What the...
- (JACKIE GRUNTS)
- (JJ GROANS)
- (BIRD SQUAWKING)
(JJ GRUNTING)
No, no, no, no!
No! I'm sorry.
- (JACKIE GRUNTING)
- (JJ THUDDING)
- (HEART MONITOR BEEPING)
- NURSE: Come on.
Nothing more you can do here.
(VENTILATOR HISSING)
(LOU SNIFFLES)
MAN: (ON RADIO) This is
crack cocaine,
seized a few days ago
by drug enforcement agents
in a park just across
the street from the mine.
Stop! Stop!
MAN: (ON RADIO) Could easily
have been heroin or PCP.
(MAN CONTINUES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
(DOG BARKING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLICKS, CLOSES)
(LIGHT SWITCH CLICKS)
(GASPS, GRUNTS)
Oh!
Oh! (BREATHING SHARPLY)
(BIRD CHIRPS)
(WHISPERS) Jack.
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
Jack, are you okay?
Baby, are you okay?
Hmm?
Jackie?
Baby, what the fuck happened?
I made it right.
(LOU SIGHS)
Oh, they're gonna
fucking fry you for this!
- Fuck.
- I'm sorry.
(LOU SIGHS)
What? Did anyone...
Did anybody see you?
Okay.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(LOU SIGHS)
Fuck.
(PANTING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(LOU EXHALES)
He's not gonna fit. I think...
I think we have to...
Let's... Let's unroll him.
- Just push. (GRUNTS)
- (JACKIE GRUNTS)
LOU: Okay.
- (GRUNTING)
- (BODY THUDDING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (BODY THUDS)
- (LOU SIGHS)
LOU: All right. We're just
gonna go for a drive, okay?
- (JACKIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (SHOVEL CLATTERS)
I know a place.
Baby, go get my truck.
Follow me, okay?
Nope.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
(SIRENS FADES OUT)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
- (SNIFFLES)
- (CAR DOOR THUDS)
- Lou-Lou. (GIGGLES)
- (LOU GASPS)
Roll your window down.
(LOU SIGHS)
Come on it's red, please.
(WINDOW RATTLING)
- DAISY: Hey, stranger.
- Daisy.
- DAISY: New ride?
- No. I mean, yeah.
How you doing?
(CHUCKLES) I'm good.
Thank you for asking.
Um, so what are you doing
out so late, huh?
Just driving,
'cause I have a headache
- and it's a migraine.
- DAISY: Poor, Lou-Lou.
(HONKS TRUCK HORN)
Ugh! Smelly cunt...
Drive around!
- (HONKING TRUCK HORN)
- DAISY: Hey.
Ain't... Ain't that
your truck?
Actually, I gotta go right now,
but we should go to Winkie's.
- Are you around tomorrow?
- Yeah. Absolutely.
- Sounds fun. I love it.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
- Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
- (ENGINE REVVING)
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
(TRUCK ENGINE REVS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(LOU GRUNTS)
(GASOLINE SPLASHING)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CAR CRASHES)
(LIQUID SWISHING)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
Lou? Are you sure?
Trust me.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(EXPLODES)
(LOU MIMICS EXPLOSION)
What is this place?
LOU: Hey, don't worry, Jack.
We're gonna be okay.
You just gotta listen
to me, okay?
You gotta do what I say.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
So, I'm gonna go back to Beth's
to make sure
we didn't leave anything.
I think you should stay here.
Why don't you pack now?
And I'll come with you.
We could make it
to Vegas by the evening.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
No, we can't go anywhere now.
Why not?
It's, um...
Hey, come here.
Come here. Come here.
Listen to me.
Someone's gonna see
that smoke. Like any minute.
And then the cops are gonna
find JJ's body.
It's okay. That's good.
'Cause there's
other shit down there.
There's other shit down there
that's gonna lead them
to someone else.
There's shit down there
that someone else
is gonna have to answer for.
Not you.
I have to go.
No, no, no, no. We have to...
- The competition's tomorrow.
- No, we have to stay here,
lay low and act real normal.
I was always gonna go.
You said you'd come with me.
Beth's safe now.
Okay.
Uh...
Can we talk about this later?
I love you.
Please stay here.
(KEYS JANGLING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(DOG BARKING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- (LOU SNIFFLES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(BIRD CHIRPING)
- (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
- (LOU SIGHS)
(WATER STIRS)
(SPRITZING)
(GLASS SQUEAKING)
(LOU GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
(CAT MEOWS)
(DOOR KNOB RATTLES)
- (DOOR THUDDING)
- (JACKIE GRUNTING)
(COFFEE POT SPUTTERING)
MAN: (OVER RADIO) This is
history in the making, folks.
The German government
said tonight they'll be making
at least a dozen
more openings in the wall,
so that more people can
cross to the West.
The excitement
in the air is palpable.
The atmosphere is electric.
A celebration of the individual.
(INDISTINCT CHEERING ON TV)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
Ah!
(CHEERING)
(JACKIE INHALES)
(MUSCLES STRETCHING)
(CROWD CHEERING ON TV)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(LOU SIGHS, SNIFFLES)
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- LOU SR: JJ!
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
JJ, you here?
We gotta talk, buddy.
(BIRD CHIRPING)
Serge.
Jeez. When's the last time
anyone took care of you?
Damn.
See anything?
- NATE: Nothing.
- (BIRD CHIRPING)
(LOU SR BLOWING AIR)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKS)
(BIRD CHIRPING)
(LOU SR EXHALES)
(CAGE CLATTERING)
LOU SR: He's not here, guys.
Let's go.
Yeah, his car's gone.
(LOU SR EXHALES)
(DOOR OPENS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- Jackie?
- (BROKEN GLASS CLINKING)
(BAG RUSTLES)
Jack.
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(JACKIE PANTING)
(PANTING CONTINUES)
(ASK ME TO DANCE MR COWBOY
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
- (INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
- (GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
You didn't know anything?
LOU SR: (SIGHS) Please.
Do they even know it's JJ?
Licence plates match.
My buddy said
it will be 24 hours,
before they can get
down there and ID the body.
- You sure it wasn't suicide?
- OFFICER MIKE: No.
Cars don't explode like that
when they crash.
Just in the movies.
(ICE CLINKING IN GLASS)
OFFICER MIKE:
With Beth in the hospital,
they're gonna be looking at you.
Who else knows about that place?
What do I pay you for?
Find out.
(LOU SIGHING)
(JACKIE LAUGHING)
Ah, fucking...
Whoo! Ah!
- (DOOR SLAMS)
- (BROKEN GLASS CLINKS)
JACKIE: (SIGHS) Whoo! Oh.
Hey baby, Lou, come on.
Pack your bags, let's go!
I'm so fucking ready! Ah!
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
- (LOU SIGHS)
(JACKIE LAUGHING)
JACKIE: Pack your bags.
We gotta go.
Mmm, God.
(SIGHS) Jesus
fucking Christ, Jack.
Where have you been?
(WATER RUNNING)
I asked for one thing.
I asked you to do one thing.
I said stay home
while I sort out everything!
How much of that stuff
did you take?
- You didn't ask.
- What?
- JACKIE: You locked me in!
- Hey, whoa!
(JACKIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Jack?
- (JACKIE MUMBLING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS) It's okay.
It's okay.
Come here.
You killed a man, Jack.
Did you get that?
Yeah. Yeah, you're welcome.
- You're fucking crazy.
- Fuck you!
Fuck you!
This isn't a game, Jack.
We need to be
so fucking careful right now.
Forget about Vegas.
- (JACKIE GRUNTS)
- Ow! Ah!
(LOU GRUNTS)
Sorry, baby.
Wish me luck.
What?
(LOU BREATHING SHAKILY)
Hey! (SIGHS)
(VAN DRIVER SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY)
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (BRAKES SQUEALING)
VAN DRIVER: Where you headin'?
JACKIE: Vegas!
VAN DRIVER: Guess it's
your lucky day.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(VAN DOOR OPENS)
VAN DRIVER: (CHUCKLES)
Good morning, sunshine.
(CHUCKLES, LICKS)
It's your stop, right?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(JACKIE SIGHS)
(VAN DRIVER
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
(GROUP SINGING)
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪  Happy birthday, dear Bobby ♪
- Oh!
- (BOBBY BLOWS AIR)
Oh, good job, kiddo. (SOBBING)
Good job.
LOU SR: Hey...
Come here, Bobby.
Mom's just a bit sad.
(SOBS) Has he called?
Has anyone heard from him?
Not yet, honey.
Lou, did you talk to him?
Did you tell him to leave?
No, no.
You promise me?
Beth, I... Yeah.
He'll be back, honey.
This guy has
a lot of thinking to do.
(BETH SOBBING)
I'll grab a soda.
(PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(COINS CLINKING)
(MACHINE CLANKING)
- (VENDING MACHINE WHIRRING)
- (CAN THUDDING)
You going to ignore me
the rest of your life?
This isn't about you or me.
This is about Beth.
She's the only fucking reason
that I'm here, Dad.
I admire how protective
you are of your sister,
but maybe next time you might be
a little more careful
how you go about it.
(LOU SCOFFS)
- What are you talking about?
- They found JJ in his car.
Yeah. Mike filled me in
on the details.
What they know so far.
Great. I'm glad Mike's doing
some actual law enforcement
for a change.
Someone burnt it up pretty bad.
Maybe they didn't know
the smoke could be seen
for miles.
An innocent act of stupidity,
or maybe there's something
you wanna tell me.
NURSE: Here she is, officers.
(KID SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
BETH: (SCREAMS) No!
(CRYING) No! No!
- (LOU SIGHS)
- BETH: I wanna see him.
(BETH CONTINUES CRYING)
I wanna see him!
(INDISTINCT WHIRRING)
OFFICER 1: What's
it like down there?
OFFICER 2:
It keeps going down! (ECHOES)
The car is just wedged here.
I'm going down
for a better look.
(GRUNTING)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
OFFICER 1: You see anything?
OFFICER 2: Fuck! There's more.
♪ I'm a bad, bad man ♪
(CROWD CHEERING)
♪ Bad, bad man ♪
♪ I'm a bad, bad man ♪
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
- (MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING)
♪ I got the moves
I'll keep it coming ♪
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
OVER SPEAKERS)
♪ If you don't like my style
Baby, I don't mind ♪
♪ I'm already thinkin'
'Bout the next in line ♪
♪ I'm a bad, bad man ♪
♪ I'm a bad, bad man... ♪
(CROWD CHEERING)
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
(SPRAY HISSING)
ANNOUNCER: (OVER SPEAKERS)
Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention please,
competitors 20 to 25,
stand on the stage, please.
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
ANNOUNCER: (ON MIC) And now...
It's the ladies!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GARBLED VOICES)
(VOICES FADE OUT)
ANNOUNCER:
Quarter turn to the right.
(JACKIE CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
ANNOUNCER: (GARBLED)
Quarter turn to the right.
(JACKIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
ANNOUNCER: (GARBLED)
Face the front.
- Thank you.
-  (CROWD CHEERING)
ANNOUNCER: (GARBLED)
Beautiful, aren't they?
And we're just getting started.
Each competitor will
return to the stage
for their individual routine.
(GARBLED ANNOUNCEMENT)
LOU: Jackie!
Fuckin' get it.
♪ Feel these hands that ♪
♪ Shape this world ♪
ANNOUNCER: Up first,
all the way from Oklahoma,
Miss Jaqueline Cleaver!
(CROWD CHEERING)
♪ When the light shines down ♪
♪ And the time goes slowly ♪
♪ When my mind's in the dust ♪
♪ Scorched and dying ♪
(CROWD CHEERING, WHISTLING)
♪ There's a penny in my hand ♪
♪ Inscribed to the sad
And lonely ♪
♪ Now I feel so cold
And alone ♪
(BONES CRACKING)
- (MUSIC SOFTENS)
- (JACKIE GASPS)
(GARBLED MUSIC PLAYING)
(JACKIE CHOKES)
(COUGHING)
(GAGGING)
(LOU GAGS)
- (GAGS, COUGHS)
- (SLIME SQUELCHING)
(LOU GRUNTS)
Baby, I told you to lay low.
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
WOMAN: Fucking fatty.
(GARBLED) Did fatty
eat too much?
- (JACKIE GRUNTING)
- (WOMEN SHOUTING)
ANNOUNCER:
Security to the stage.
(JACKIE GRUNTING)
BOUNCER: Knock it off!
- Stop! (SCREAMING)
- BOUNCER: Uh! Come on!
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
- (BRAKES SQUEALING)
- (LOU SIGHS)
DAISY: I was waiting
for you at Winkie's last night.
Oh, yeah?
Sorry, I was, uh,
with my sister.
She's, you know,
in the hospital.
It's been a whole thing.
- (FRIDGE DOOR CLOSES)
- DAISY: Oh, yeah.
I... I... I heard about
what happened to B.
Actually, I, um...
I brought you
a little something.
It's just a little something
to... to cheer you up.
I can't imagine how
you must be feeling right.
That's nice.
Um, you know, I... I quit.
All of it.
Oh, my gosh. Lou-Lou!
Do... Do you want me to stop?
No, but I just don't need this.
You should keep it.
- No, save it.
- (LIGHTER CLANKS)
For an emergency.
(LOU SIGHS)
Sure was weird seeing you
the other night.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah. I was even
thinking about you
as I was walking along there.
I don't know why. It's just
a crazy coincidence, I guess.
- Crazy. (CHUCKLES)
- DAISY: Mmm-hmm.
Or fate.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
I did wanna ask you
one thing, though,
and I understand if maybe
it's none of my business.
No, please. What?
What was she doing
driving your truck?
Who?
You know,
that big girl. (CHUCKLES)
Thought you two were,
maybe, together or something.
(SPUTTERING) I... I... I...
I'm not with her.
It's, like, she's
somebody that I...
I haven't seen her in a while.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, it's a weird coincidence
that she was behind me.
Yeah, I thought
it was weird, too.
And that
you were driving JJ's car.
(LOU SIGHS)
We hung out a couple of times.
(CHUCKLES)
I never forget a Camaro.
(LOU LAUGHS)
(GLASS THUDS)
(INDISTINCT WHIRRING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
- (THUDS)
- (CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
OFFICER 2: Court appearance is
in eight days. (GARBLED)
Bail is set at $300.
You get one phone call.
(OFFICER 2 SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(LINE RINGING)
DAISY: (OVER PHONE)
Lou's residence. Howdy.
Who's this?
DAISY: Stay away from her.
She doesn't want you anymore.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DAISY HUMMING HAPPILY)
OFFICER: All right, Rambo.
Your guardian angel's here.
(KEYS JANGLING)
LOU SR: You and Lou fall out
or something? (MUFFLED)
That why you called me?
Don't worry.
You made the right call.
My guys will take care
of this whole problem.
You know, Lou and I have had
our share of arguments too.
I bet she's told you
all kinds of things about me.
That's her right.
Although, I find it
a little rich at times.
I own the gym.
She probably didn't
tell you that.
I know you didn't ask
for my advice,
but seeing how you're
sitting in my car,
I get to tell you anyway...
You can't go
around killin' people
without figuring out
a few of the details first,
you know what I mean?
Um, I wanna get out now, please.
I wanna get out.
All right, get out
if you want to.
What do you think this is?
But once you're out of this car,
you're on your own.
You know that, don't you?
I mean, really alone.
They found the body, the cops.
They're gonna ask questions.
You really don't think
I have anything better to do?
Hmm? I came out here
to help you.
Both of you.
You know, Lou won't
ask me for it.
She thinks she has
it all under control,
but she can't handle
a thing like this.
You're smarter than that.
I know you are.
Lou didn't do anything.
Why don't you close the door?
It's cold out there.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
LOU SR: Call me
when it's done.
You try and get some sleep now.
(JACKIE SIGHS)
(DAISY SLURPING)
Thank you.
- (HUMMING)
- (HONEY SQUELCHING)
Ooh! (CHUCKLES)
You sure you're not hungry?
Yeah, I... I just wanna be
boring for a second.
- And, uh...
- What is it?
I just wanna clear the air
on this whole JJ thing.
Well, he really had it coming,
didn't he?
Well, I mean, we weren't
friends or anything,
but it's pretty horrible.
What happened to him, you know?
I thought you were saying
how much you hated him.
Yeah, but I didn't
want him dead.
He was family.
Okay.
You know how we ran
into each other
at the lights the other night?
DAISY: Mmm-hmm.
Did you tell anyone about that?
Like the cops or anyone?
(SUCKS ON FINGERS)
I was thinking about it.
What were you thinking
of saying?
I thought they ought to know
that I saw that beefy girl
driving JJ's car that night.
But you didn't
'cause she wasn't.
- Wasn't she?
- No.
Sorry, I... I thought
you'd be pleased.
You said you weren't
together anymore.
- No, we're... we're not.
- That why you brought me here?
No, no. Hey.
I'm just...
Hey, I'm... I'm just looking
out for myself, you know.
Think about it,
if you tell the cops that
you saw her driving JJ's car,
they're gonna start
asking around.
They're gonna find out
we were dating,
that... that she was
staying with me.
And... And it would be
a whole thing.
And I don't wanna
get dragged into it,
because I'm...
I'm scared, Daze.
(DAISY GASPS)
Oh...
My God, Lou-Lou,
I'm... I'm such a dum-dum.
I didn't think of that.
Hey, it's okay.
You were just trying to help.
- DAISY: Mmm-hmm.
- I appreciate it.
Don't talk to anyone.
Especially the cops, okay?
- 'Cause...
- Okay.
I actually don't even know
anything about what happened
to JJ that night.
He got smashed in the head
and set on fire, apparently.
Okay, so if anyone asks you,
you didn't see Jackie,
anywhere that night, right?
Must've been some other freak.
- Exactly.
- (DAISY CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Thanks, Daisy.
God, I'm fucking starving now.
All right!
(GASPS) Oh, let's
order margaritas.
- All right.
- (GIGGLES) Excuse me.
(TAPPING FINGERS)
♪ Two margaritas please! ♪
- (SERVER LAUGHS)
- (DAISY GIGGLES)
LOU: So you're just getting
your things right?
Gotta go pick up Beth.
(DAISY CHUCKLING)
Hey, look. Hey, look.
Need to go
to the hospital, okay?
(DAISY RETCHES)
(BLOOD SQUELCHING)
(DAISY THUDS)
I'm... I'm... Baby.
I'm not... This isn't...
- (GUN CLICKS)
- I'm not.
Huh? (GASPS)
Baby, what the fuck
are you doing?
- (METAL BARS CLANK)
- Fuck. Fuck!
Jack! (EXHALES)
Holy, fuck.
(BREATHES SHARPLY)
Shit!
(JACKIE BREATHING SHAKILY)
- (TRUCK HONKING HORN)
- (BRAKES SCREECHING)
Fuck! Fuck!
(LOU BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PHONE RINGING)
LOU SR: Yeah?
JACKIE: (OVER PHONE)
It's done.
(VOICE BREAKS)
She was with Lou.
(FLOOR SQUEAKING)
- (LOU GRUNTING)
- (FLOOR SQUEAKS)
(LOU GRUNTS)
(COINS CLINKING)
(LINE RINGING)
- HUGHEY: (OVER PHONE) Hello?
-  (SOFTLY) Hughey.
HUGHEY: Jackie.
Mom said you ran away.
What's going on?
(SOBS) Don't ever
fall in love, okay.
Okay, Hughey.
It hurts. (SOBBING)
Just don't ever
fall in love. (CRYING)
WOMAN: (OVER PHONE)
Hughey, who is it?
HUGHEY: Jackie.
WOMAN: Give me the phone.
Give me that.
Jacqueline, you stay away
from us, you monster!
Don't ever call
this house again!
(RECEIVER CLANKS)
(LOU GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERS NERVOUSLY)
(GRUNTS)
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- O'RILEY: FBI, open up.
AGENT: This is the FBI,
Miss Langston.
(LOU BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
(LOU GRUNTS)
(BODY SQUELCHING)
O'RILEY: Miss Langston,
I need you to open the door now.
AGENT: Jesus Christ.
- (BUCKET CLANKS)
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
AGENT: Open the fucking door.
Hey. Hey, sorry,
one sec, uh...
O'RILEY: We just wanna talk.
(CHAIN CLANKS)
- Hey. (SIGHS)
- You gonna let us in?
You didn't really catch me
at the greatest time. (PANTS)
(BREATHES SHARPLY)
O'RILEY: It's about
your brother-in-law.
We really need to talk to you.
We won't take long.
(CHAIN CLANKS)
O'RILEY: Nice place.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
O'RILEY: You talked
to your dad recently?
I told you, we don't talk.
O'RILEY: Is that right?
When your brother-in-law's
remains were recovered,
forensics also found these.
We suspect they're people
who threatened your dad
and his operation.
We've been trying
to shut him down
for a while now.
But as soon as someone
starts talking,
they have a habit
of disappearing.
Your brother-in-law was
the latest.
Real shame what happened to him.
Lost us our best informant.
Guess your dad caught wind, huh?
(SCOFFS) I'm not involved
in any of his shit.
But you were, weren't you?
(LOU BREATHING HEAVILY)
Quite the sidekick,
we were told.
We've been trying to locate
your mom for a while now.
Wanted to ask her
what she remembers.
The last record we could find
- was from 12 years ago.
- (LOU SNIFFLING)
It says she contacted
local police saying
that she wanted to talk
to 'em about her husband.
She never followed up.
Um...
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(JACKIE GRUNTS)
(UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
(GUN COCKING)
(PHONE RINGING)
LOU: Hmm.
LOU SR: (OVER PHONE)
The bullshit stops
now, Louise.
Now you just listen up
and do exactly as I tell you.
- You ready?
- I... Pfft... Huh?
I removed the witness
connecting you to JJ.
I protected you.
Not that I'm dumb enough
to expect gratitude for it.
(VOICE BREAKS)
You made her do that.
Well, she was
in a tight spot last night.
You should've helped her out.
(LOU SNIFFLES)
- Where is she?
- LOU SR: I have her.
She'll be arrested
for double homicide,
and this whole mess
will blow over.
- (LOU BREATHING SHAKILY)
- LOU SR: The cops are gonna
wanna talk to you.
Just tell them
you guys were having
some fun together,
you're horrified...
If you hurt her,
I'm gonna kill you.
LOU SR: Lou,
shut the hell up, and listen.
Unless you wanna answer
for that dead body
- in your apartment.
- LOU: Ugh!
I need you to sit tight
and do absolutely nothing.
I know you can manage that.
Just sit back.
Let Dad take care
- of everything.
- (RECEIVER CLANKING)
LOU: No fucking way.
What did you think
was gonna happen, Lou?
I'd be arrested
for a murder I didn't commit.
What did you think
was gonna happen?
(SNIFFLES)
How many people are
down there, huh?
Seemed like a lot in those days.
Did you keep it up?
No one can connect me to bones.
I can.
Are you threatening me?
(LOU CLICKS TONGUE)
Yep. (SIGHS)
Yeah, let her go
or I'm gonna call
the Feds right now,
and tell them
everything you ever did.
How's that sound, Dad?
(SNIFFLING)
Hmm?
Dad?
LOU SR: That was
really stupid, honey.
- (CALL DISCONNECTS)
- (DIAL TONE BEEPING)
(RECEIVER THUDS)
(RECEIVER CLICKS)
(LOU SR SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
- (YELLING)
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
- (CRUNCHING)
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(PHONE RINGING)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
BETH: (OVER SPEAKER)
Lou. Lou, are you there?
I'm waiting for you.
Please come and get me.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (GUN COCKS)
- (DOOR CREAKS)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(BLINDS CLATTERING)
(CAT MEOWS)
(LOU SIGHS)
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (SHOTS FIRING)
- OFFICER MIKE: Lou!
(OFFICER MIKE GROANS)
(FIRING STOPS)
(OFFICER MIKE GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
He sent you to kill me?
Fuck you, you rat!
- (LOU GRUNTS)
- (OFFICER MIKE GROANS)
(LOU PANTING)
(OFFICER MIKE GROANS)
(LOU GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING) Oh, God!
(STAIRS CLANKING)
(LOU GRUNTS)
(CAT MEOWS)
(ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(THUNDER CRACKING)
- (INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
- SHARON: Just get in the car.
LOU: Hey, Sharon.
Just ruining everything.
Oh!
(CAR ENGINE TURNS OVER)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(OPERA SONG PLAYING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(LOU SIGHS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- LOU: Jackie?
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(LOU SIGHS) I'm sorry,
- I didn't pick you up.
- Don't.
I don't... I don't know
what he told you.
Lou, he was my husband.
- I know.
- (BETH SOBS)
And I'm... I'm sorry, but...
I... I'm... I'm not sorry.
(BETH SCREAMING)
- (LOU GRUNTING)
- (BETH SCREAMS)
(LOU GRUNTING)
- What the fuck, Lou?
- I just...
BETH: (SCREAMS)
What the fuck? Why?
(SOBBING)
(LOU PANTING)
- Why?
- (BETH SIGHS)
Because he was
gonna kill you one day.
(BETH BREATHING HEAVILY)
You... don't know
anything about love.
I'm so sorry for you.
I love... you. I love you.
(SCOFFS) Fuck off.
Wow.
You're a...
moron.
(SIGHS) Where are...
Where are they?
(EXHALES) Daddy's not here.
Really?
Where is she Beth?
- I don't know.
- Bethany!
BETH: (SCREAMS)
Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
You wanna tell me where she is?
- Ow!
- Huh?
Do you wanna be honest?
Do you wanna be honest with me?
Stop! Stop!
- Where is she?
- Fucking monster.
- In the corn house.
- LOU: Love you, sis!
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
- (OPERA SONG CONTINUES)
- Jack!
- (THUNDER RUMBLES)
- (LOU GRUNTS)
Jackie.
(PANTING)
- Oh, no!
- (JACKIE MUMBLING)
Oh, my God.
Just... Just one second.
- (JACKIE CRIES)
- LOU: Sorry,
my family's so fucked!
(JACKIE CRYING)
I got you, I got you.
Hold on, baby.
(JACKIE CRIES, SCREAMS)
LOU: Ow!
What are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
- (LOU MUMBLES)
- (JACKIE GRUNTS)
LOU: Hey, I'm trying to...
JACKIE: (GRUNTS) Fuck!
LOU: Hey, come here.
JACKIE: Get off of me.
- LOU: Oh, God. Hey...
- Let me go!
I'm helping you.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- Oh! Baby, what the fuck?
- You're selling me out?
How am I selling you out?
I... I love you.
(GUNSHOT FIRES)
Don't lie to me.
- LOU: No, I'm not.
- No, you couldn't wait
one night before you fucked
someone else!
Daisy? I did that for you.
She was gonna tell.
- Oh!
- (GUNSHOT FIRES)
- You want me to thank you?
- LOU: No, I'm...
Baby, I'm just saying
it wasn't like that.
If I was selling you out,
I'd be telling the cops
everything right now.
I'm not! I've got
Daisy's body in my truck.
I was gonna get rid of it
before anyone found out.
I mean, Christ, I am...
I am really trying...
- (FIRING GUNSHOTS)
- JACKIE: Oh, fuck!
I wish I never
met you. (CRIES)
(GRUNTS, BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(LOU PANTING)
I killed people, Lou.
I know.
(CRIES) I don't know
what's wrong with me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey...
There is absolutely nothing...
- (GUN CLATTERS)
- wrong with you.
You are the most amazing,
most incredible,
beautiful person I've ever met
in my whole life.
(JACKIE SOBS)
He deserved it.
What about her?
My dad made you do it.
He does that.
You didn't have a choice, okay?
(JACKIE BREATHING SHAKILY)
I fucking love you, you idiot.
I love you too.
(LOU EXHALES)
(BOTH CRYING)
JACKIE: What's gonna
happen to us?
You're gonna
be okay. (SNIFFLES)
You just have to listen
to me this time, you got it?
Can you do that?
Okay. (SNIFFLES)
LOU: Hmm.
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
LOU: Okay, here's
what's gonna happen.
You go that way,
there's a back road.
Wait for me there.
Stay out of sight.
Make sure no one sees you.
What about you?
LOU: I'll be fine. There's
something I gotta do first.
Feds are gonna be
here in two minutes.
Get the fuck out of here. Go!
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
LOU: Dad?
Where the fuck are you?
Hey!
- (GUN FIRES)
- (LOU YELLS)
Ow! Ah!
(GRUNTING)
- LOU SR: Drop it.
- (GUN FIRES)
You ungrateful brat.
- (GRUNTS)
- (LOU GROANING)
God. Well...
(SIGHS) It's over, man.
I told them everything.
You have no idea
what you've done.
Uh, yes, I do.
I've done the right thing
for the first time
- in my whole life, Dad.
- Oh, Jesus.
- You sound like your mother.
- Shut up!
You killed her, didn't you?
I get it. She was gonna tell.
I just wanna know.
Did you do it yourself,
or did you have Mike do it?
Your mom left
because she couldn't
stand being a wife to me,
- and a mother to you.
- (LOU GROANS)
You fucking liar.
I'm nothing like you.
That'd be nice wouldn't it?
(CRIES) Stop lying.
LOU SR: Oh...
(SHUSHING)
- (LOU SCREAMS)
- (JACKIE GASPS)
LOU: Let go of me!
- (JACKIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (LOU SCREAMING)
(BONES CRACKING)
(LOU SCREAMS)
(MUSCLES STRETCHING)
- (LOU PANTING)
- (LOU SR SHUSHING)
It's okay.
- (GUN COCKS)
- Come on.
- LOU SR: It's okay.
- Dad...
LOU SR: Everyone learns
the hard way.
It's the ones you love
the most that always
disappoint you in the end.
- (LOU WINCES)
- JACKIE: Get off her!
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
What the fuck?
(GROANS)
(LOU SR YELLING)
Oh, wow!
(LOU SR GRUNTING)
(MUMBLING)
- (BONES CRACKING)
- (LOU SR GROANING)
(GROANING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTING)
LOU SR: Lou, help me.
(LOU GRUNTING)
You know what?
I love you, too.
(LOU SR GAGGING)
You sick fuck!
They're coming.
Just finish it.
LOU SR: (GARBLED) No.
JACKIE: Come on.
- (SIRENS BLARING)
- (LOU SR MUMBLING)
- (GUN COCKS)
- (LOU SIGHS)
LOU: Bye, Dad.
(TRANSCENDENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(JACKIE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
(METAL THUDDING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(DAISY BREATHING SOFTLY)
(WHISPER BY MARTIN REV
PLAYING)
(DAISY CHOKING)
(MUSIC FADES OUT)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)